[{"answer": "I think you and I could walk out of here and within about 90 seconds of yelling, looking, at least someone come toward us and probably somewhere within five minutes of that, probably west of here, we'd both be able to take care of whatever we needed.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "All of these years later, 40 years of drug war, would either of us have difficulty anywhere in the United States finding our former drug of choice within 45 minutes?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Part of the problem is drug addiction tends to be a serial matter and it's not easy to fix and people say treatment doesn't work, and in fact it doesn't.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "So, David Carr, why do you think if we have had actual Hamsterdams, what would America look like or do we have them already?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "This is over $300 or $600 million.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Six tons, whole sale value?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Yes, kilo blocks.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "So these are all kilo blocks?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, whenever I feel somebody's hands up my skirt I'm always sort of interested in what exactly they are trying to find up there.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Do you have a problem with this?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Well, what does metadata mean to you?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, you know --", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "What does it mean to you, David Simon?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "My concern is that --", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "-- misuse this information?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Tony, if they want --", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Well, I mean, who knows more about you, the NSA or Amazon?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "I've not been to either place.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "If you had to spend the rest of your life in Russia or Venezuela, where would you pick?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, totally.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "I should try it?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "You're not loving it, are you?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "It depends.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Mario Batali, what do you think?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Yes, I was.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Deeply traumatizing experience and you certainly were a product of that system, and in fact you yourself, at some point in your career early on as a chef, well, you were a miserable son of a bitch yourself, weren't you, Mr. Ripert?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Love and kiss and stuff like that.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "It's all peace and love?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly don't think you want to be serving cancerous food to your customers, if you know what that is.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Does -- does it matter?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Right, but not alcoholic, yes.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "If they want to kill themselves with food, it's OK with you?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "So you wouldn't cut them off?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Even with -- even with we were skinny, we were not doing a very good job at smoking the terrorists out of their holes.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "How are we going to -- how are we going to raise a giraffe or smoke terrorists out of their holes if we're -- we're too fat to squeeze in after it?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Have another piece of cake.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "So I should really -- I should have another piece of cake?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I think 20 percent is pretty much the standard.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "And where do you really start to get into offensive?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I don't get bad service anywhere.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "That said, when was the last time you got bad service?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "This is one-third gin, one-third sweet Italian vermouth and one-third campari.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "What's in this cocktail?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "And how did we get to bologna (ph) anyway?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "I think that's a little short to be quite frank.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "I would have brutally kicked his ass.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "...how would you respond?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "(ph): Well, yes.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "I just think (ph) -- the real question is, what if your buddies put that on the internet?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "It was one of his pals that were there, right?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "All right, last question.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Pee (ph) in a bucket?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "I feel no guilt about pleasure, first of all.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Many you had one too many, the bronies (ph), what -- what dirty, shameful thing do you find yourself craving to eat?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "You had a cronut?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "I've had a cronut.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "You've -- you've had one?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "So a cronut is a -- something we launched on the menu in (ph) May (ph).", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "What -- what is a cronut?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I've cut the line twice.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "So do you have -- do you cut the line at -- at Dominique's Place now that you helped turn this into a Frankenstein monster?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Yes, no.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "And I tell myself saying, if I could -- if I had a time machine, I would like to go back to 2004 and not have stopped, you know?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "Oh, I would keep going.", "docId": "130725pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "You would have kept going or you would have stopped?", "qSentId": 654}]